威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们来看看这个美丽的概念,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We're on
to the beautiful concept of,
关于闭包的优雅概念，因为我们涉及到词法范围和
the elegant concept of closure,
as we involve lexical scoping and
执行上下文。
execution context.
它们之间的根本区别在于,
And the fundamental
difference between them,
我们大多数人都没有意识到。
that most of us don't really realize.
但是这个背景会为它画上句号所以我们开始,
But it's gonna be the backdrop on
which closes it, so here we go,
我认为这是 JavaScript 中最深奥的概念。
I think this is the most
esoteric concept in JavaScript.
如果你真的明白，我想你会找到工作的,
This is the bit that If you really
understand, I think you'll get jobs,
毫无疑问。
no doubt about it.
这是一个特殊的部分，如果你也能理解的话,
This is a special bit,
if you understand it as well,
你可以做一些非常强大的事情。
you can do some really powerful things.
你可以建立专业级别的功能，像一次，这是一个功能，可以
You can build professional level functions
like once, this is a function that can
将其他函数转换为只运行一次的函数。
turn other functions into
functions that are gonna run once.
如果它们再次运行，它们就不起作用了，你可能会想,
If they run them again, they don't work,
and already, you might be thinking,
等等，这说不通，因为我知道函数是怎么工作的。
hold on, that doesn't make sense,
because I know how functions work.
他们不记得之前跑步的任何事情,
They don't remember anything
from their previous running,
每次都是全新的，我们想要那样。
they're brand new every time,
we want that.
但是，等一下，我告诉你，他们会记得他们已经逃跑了
And yet, hold on, I'm telling you they're
gonna somehow remember they've been run
不要再跑了。
before, and not run again.
我们可以在年、年和年实现记忆、核心性能优化器
We can achieve memorization,
a core performance optimizer in, and
这是我之前说过的,
this is something I talked about,
you know,
现在最重要的资产是开发者时间。
the most important asset
now is developer time.
我会说这种记忆仍然是一个需要练习的方法
I will say this memorization
is still a go to practice for
优化我们如何编写代码，性能如何。
optimizing how we write our code,
how performance it is.
这样我们就不会重复任务,
That's going to enable
us to not repeat tasks,
如果我们以前做过，就不会重复耗时的计算。
not repeat calculations that take
a long time if we've done them before.
Will Sentance: 许多设计模式的工作，比如在模块模式中
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Many jobs of design
patterns like in the module pattern that
使用一个结点使用闭包，然后，我只是基本上列出了他们在这里。
use a node uses closure, and then,
I just basically listed them all off here.
迭代器、部分应用程序、运行、在异步中维护状态
Iterators, partial application, carrying,
maintaining state in an asynchronous
所有剩下的就是理解引擎盖下的结束,
world, all of the rest on
understanding closure under the hood,
我们不打算实施这些东西。
we're not going to
implementing these things,.
伙计们，你们可以进入所有困难的部分，关于执行所有这些事情,
You can go to all the hard parts, folks,
about implementing all those things,
实际上，你知道，我们将实现一个同步的。
actually that, you know,,we will
be implementing a synchronous one.
但是他们都依赖于结束，所以
But they all depend on closure, so
这一切都始于我们提醒自己，我们之前看到的这些原则。
it all starts with us reminding ourselves
of these principles we saw earlier on.
我不认为我们会一头扎进去，我们能接受吗？
I don't think we're going to go through
and dive on how to get, can we take that?
不，我们不能再来一次，但是，我们知道每次一个函数
No, we can't take that again, but,
we do know that every time a function gets
执行，运行，作为调用调用，它创建一个全新的本地内存。
executed, run, invoke as an invocation,
it creates a brand new local memory.
记住，一个全新的执行上下文作为一个小的临时存储内存,
Remember, a brand new execution context
as a little temporary store memory,
当我们运行完那个函数后，这些都被删除了。
when we finish running that function,
that's all deleted.
我们再次运行这个函数，它不记得以前的运行,
We run the function again,
it doesn't remember the previous running,
数据存储在先前运行的函数，事实上,
the data stored in the previous
running of the function, In fact,
如果有的话，那也太老了。
it would be pretty old if it did.
我不想用2乘以7然后有记忆,
I don't want to run multiply by two with
seven, and then kind of have a memory,
一个关于它之前和七个一起运行的幻想。
a reverie over it previously
being run with seven.
我们希望它是新鲜的运行与十，这是很好的，我们不希望输入数字为
We want it to be fresh to run with ten,
that's good, we don't want input number to
上面有七个印记，我想重新开始，事实也的确如此。
sort of have an imprint of seven on it and
I want to start fresh and it does.
函数从来不会记住它们以前运行的任何东西，即本地内存
Functions never remember anything from
their previous running, that local memory
在运行过程中产生的数量乘以2每次都是新鲜的。
that gets created inside the running
multiply by two, fresh every time.
然而，如果我们也有这个功能会怎样
And yet,
what if we could have that function also
有永久的记忆吗？
have a permanent memory attached to it?
这可能会改变我们写代码的方式,
That could change everything
about how we write code,
让我们看看，有记忆的功能。
let's see, functions with memories.
当我们的函数被调用的时候，我们创建一个生命存储的数据,
When our function gets called invoked,we
create a little life store of data,
我们称之为局部内存，我们可以称之为可变环境。
we call it local memory,
we might call it variable environment.
我之前没有说过，但是我会继续写下去
I didn't say this earlier on,
but I'm gonna draw on for
等一下，假设我乘以2(7)
a sec, suppose I run multiply by 2 (7)
这是本地内存，在它的本地内存中,
here's local memory, in its local memory,
我会找到输入数字设置为7，好吧。
I will find input number set to 7, okay.
那个本地内存，当我运行完这个函数，它就被删除了,
That local memory, when I finish
running this function, that is deleted,
除了返回的值。
except for the returned value.
本地内存的另一个名称是它的变量环境,
Another name for that local memory
is its variable environment,
环境就是我身边的东西，对吗？
environment is the stuff around me, right?
这是我的环境，你在我的环境,
This my environment here,
you're in my environment,
这些是变量，或者常量，或者函数
where these are the variables, or
constants, or functions that are in and
在这个函数里面，我可以在函数里面。
around me inside this function,
available to me inside the function.
顺便说一句，他们有时也把这叫做本地记忆,
They also sometimes, by the way,
call this local memory,
我现在只想告诉你们这些，作为奖励，他们称之为国家。
I just wanna tell you this stuff now,
as a bonus, they call it state.
无论何时你听到国家这个词，它都是一个非常奇怪的词,
Whenever you hear about the term state,
it's one of those really bizarre terms,
也就是说，在那个特定时刻的实时数据,
that just means,
the live data at that particular moment,
在我的申请表里，这些信息都被存储了。
given moment in my application,
that's being stored.
所以我的应用程序状态，在这一点上,
So my application state,
and at that point,
我的函数状态是输入数字7这是我的状态，就是这样。
my function's state is input number is 7,
that's my state, that's it.
所以当函数结束时，我们也可以把这个状态称为函数的状态
So we can call this the state as well of
the function, when the function finishes
运行时，其本地内存将被删除，除了所有返回的值。
running, its local memory is deleted,
except for any returned value.
但是，如果我们的函数在执行过程中保留了活动数据，又会怎样呢？
But what if our functions could hold
on to live data during their execution?
如果我有一些数据不会被自动删除,
What if I could have some of that data,
not be deleted automatically,
不会被退回，但是不知怎么的坚持下来了。
not be returned, but
somehow persisted and held onto.
这样，下次我运行这个函数时，它可以有一些内存，一些
Such that the next time I run this
function, it can have some memory, some
回忆起之前的死刑，想象一下那会让我们做什么。
remembrance of its previous execution,
imagine what that would allow us to do.
这样我们的函数定义，函数定义本身,
That would let our function definitions,
the function definition itself,
注意，当我们运行它有一点内存。
notice when we run it
have a little memory.
但是这个定义本身有一个持久的记忆
But the definition itself have
a persistent memory attached like
一个永久的记忆附在上面。
a permanent memory attached onto it.
那将是非常非常特别的让我们可以做一些事情，比如说,
That would be really, really special that
would allow us to do things like say,
你之前运行过这个函数。
you've previously run this function.
我之所以知道是因为在我对以前跑步的回忆中,
I know that because in my
remembrance of the previous running,
我已经拖延，你以前运行我，所以你不能再次运行我。
I've stalled that you previously run me,
so you can't run me again.
所以我可以限制一个函数只运行一次
So I can limit a function
to only run one time and
我们还会看到更多的东西。
a thousand more things we're gonna see.